[OVERDO]
[Episode 11]
Why are you here?
This is a photo of your adoptive mother.
Why burn it?
She was trapped
in the Li family her whole life.
Now that she’s gone,
I couldn’t let her
stay trapped in the Li family’s shadow.
Then why not keep it?
I’m not her real child.
What about Li Boze?
Li Boze deserves it even less.
Was your adoptive mother...
good to you?
On the contrary.
She treated me very badly.
After taking the wrong child,
the older I got,
the less I looked like Li Rongzhang.
I was considered a bastard.
She couldn't defend herself.
Driven crazy by
Li Rongzhang's torment,
she took all her resentment out on me.
But she was also the only one
who, when I was beaten
unconscious by Li Rongzhang,
would apply medicine to my wounds.
Do you know
why Li Rongzhang made me eat raw meat?
Why?
It was also a rainy day.
My adoptive mother had just passed away.
I was all alone in the huge Li residence,
feeling very lonely.
By coincidence, I found
a stray puppy in the backyard.
I felt
it was just like me
and wanted to adopt it.
Little did I know...
Father.
Where did you get that?
Give it to me.
No.
Give it to me!
No!
Lock him up.
Don't give him any food.
Give me back my dog!
Give it back!
I found it in the backyard!
Give it back to me!
Just like that,
he starved me for 3 days.
Three days later,
that door finally opened.
My expression when I saw the raw meat
was exactly the same as yours now.
This was the way Li Rongzhang
wanted to teach me to survive.
In the face of survival,
nothing else matters.
I was taught this way
by him for 12 years.
You don't need to pity me.
I just can't control
my body's instinctive reaction to him.
But at least
I can resist the fear.
Isn't it starting to work now?
It's not pity.
I just understand you.
He destroyed you,
but he also molded you.
In front of its creator,
a piece of work
is utterly defenseless.
Yes.
You are right.
He is a monster.
Raised by him,
I am a monster too.
That's why
three years ago,
I could sense
something fishy in your letter.
You and I
are essentially the same kind of people.
Maybe what you are doing now
has something to do
with Xiaolan back then.
It has nothing to do with you.
Ren Susu,
no one in this world
understands you better than I do.
You can tell me everything.
Having an ally
is better than fighting alone.
I don't need allies.
Alright.
Fine.
Since we can't be allies,
then I must warn you.
Turn yourself in,
or leave Murong Qingyu.
Otherwise,
you'll bear the consequences.
Have you forgotten the lesson
of the blood wedding dress already?
You really never learn.
I'll say it again—
mind your own business.
Mind my own business?
At the Li family just now,
who was minding my business?
You helped me last time,
so I was returning the favor this time.
♪ In exchange for my everything ♪
♪ Will you finally be mine? ♪
♪ Give me love and hate ♪
♪ I can't break free, I can't escape ♪
♪ This, too, can be called
a lifetime together ♪
♪ We ♪
♪ Remain bound by fate until the end ♪
♪ Forevermore ♪
Young Master Boze.
Be careful not to catch a cold.
I'm fine.
Is Qingyi back?
Dudu?
Why did you come over
in the rain so late at night?
Mother.
Look at you.
You're soaked.
Hurry up and prepare
a set of dry clothes
for Young Master Boze.
Also,
make some ginger soup.
I'll go right away.
Come.
You don't need to worry about him.
He's used to being free.
Who knows if he'll come back.
Mother,
do you know
what happened to Qingyi at the Li family?
Li Rongzhang
always thought Qingyi
didn't look like him,
so he suspected your biological mother
of infidelity.
He thought Qingyi was a bastard
and beat him frequently.
Later, we found out
that the 2 families had mixed up
our babies.
You were still young then,
and I couldn't bear to just send you back.
So you and Qingyi
weren't switched back immediately.
But the way Li Rongzhang treated him
couldn't be changed.
It has always been like this.
But Mother,
later, didn't you also...
He deserved it.
They were torturing each other.
Why should I care?
But Qingyi is your biological son.
Back then,
he clearly heard
the news that Li Rongzhang
was going to assassinate your father,
but he failed to explain it clearly.
And that caused your father's death!
After your father died,
he woke up and shouted, "Watch out!"
What was the point?
Mother.
The incident 12 years ago
was not caused by my father
from the Li family.
Qingyi was too young at that time,
and he didn't see
who was behind it clearly.
So there is no evidence for this.
Even if there's no evidence,
he had a motive.
Alright.
It's raining heavily outside,
so don't go back today.
Finish the ginger soup
and go take a rest.
Okay.
[Zarry Grand Hotel]
Boss Hai, you're here.
Please come in.
We've saved a table for you.
These wealthy families
have been shocking me every single day.
Could it be
that Li Boze did it on purpose?
He knows the relationship between
Li Rongzhang and Murong Qingyi,
so he intentionally intensified
the conflict.
It couldn't be.
With his simple mind,
he couldn't do such a thing.
You've only met him a few times,
but you seem to know him quite well.
Life is like a play.
I've played so many roles
and sung about so many hearts.
A young master like Li Boze,
who can be seen through at a glance,
is the easiest to read.
But I must remind you.
Both of them are sons of the two families,
but Murong Qingyi's thoughts
are so deep
that they can't be seen through.
You chased after him to the Li family
probably out of pity for him again, right?
I just didn't want to drag him
into this again.
What if he reveals your identity
to Murong Qingyu?
Don't worry.
I am prepared.
Tao?
Why are you here?
He has been looking for you.
I was afraid of arousing suspicion,
so I just let him come here.
Don't worry, Sister.
We older kids
are usually sent out
to beg during the day.
No one is watching us these days,
so no one will find out.
Eat up.
Why are you looking for us?
The orphanage is sending out goods again.
At a time like this,
they still dare to do this?
There's only what you can't imagine,
nothing they wouldn't dare to do.
What kind of goods?
Pretty girls.
Those people dress them in skirts
and lock them in the building of the new orphanage.
It's the premium goods
whose whereabouts
we could never track down.
Over the years,
the girls who were sold to rich families
and brothels
could always be tracked down.
But the most beautiful girls
have completely disappeared.
We've been investigating for so long,
and we still don't even know
where their black market is.
Last time, because of Murong Qingyi,
I failed to get information
about the Elite Club from Li Rongzhang.
You suspect this club
is related to the Huo family's business?
This Elite Club
is single-handedly run by the Huo family.
The entry requirements are strict,
and the information
is strictly confidential.
With a fixed buyer group
and confidential trading channels,
what do you think
they are trading?
Tao,
here. Take this.
Take this as what you begged for today.
From now on,
we should not contact each other anymore.
Even if you get news,
don't rush to find us.
Protect yourself.
Understand?
Yes.
Thank you, Sister.
Go now.
Goodbye, Sisters.
This child is quite clever.
What should we do now?
It's an eventful time.
These girls from the orphanage
won't be locked up for long.
Notify the sisters
to keep a close eye on the orphanage.
I will try to find another way
through the Li family.
With something like this happening,
the police station cannot escape blame.
The police station is going through
a leadership transition right now.
The Huo family has a say in this.
Inspector Li has already sent someone
to investigate.
Young Master Huo.
This little girl
was also there that night.
She stopped me
and insisted on singing for me.
Let me ask you,
where did Nanny Sun go
that night?
Nanny Sun ran off with a man.
These brats!
Why so fierce?
Can't you talk nicely?
Is this your doll?
It's so cute.
Tell me,
why did you sing for them that night?
Nanny told us to practice singing.
Then when did Nanny
have you practice in the yard?
Right...
Right before bedtime.
I want to hear it too.
Can you sing it for me?
Wait!
Well...
You!
-Come here.
-Come here!
Do you know where Nanny Sun went?
I know.
Nanny Sun ran off with a man.
Who said that?
The janitor,
the plump auntie,
and Sister He from the senior class.
They all said so.
Those gossiping busybodies.
Go!
It's sweet?
Did you see?
Young Master Qingyu and Miss Fang's
wedding outfits have arrived.
I heard they were made
by a foreign tailor.
They're magnificent.
Are your injuries better?
I won't die.
Have you made up your mind?
About what?
The two choices I gave you.
Miss Fang,
where do you want to try on
the wedding dress?
I'll do it right here.
Go to the study and call Qingyu over.
Yes.
Try it on here?
Aren't you afraid
I'll expose you here?
Just try it.
Very good.
Qingyu.
Mother.
Is this your wedding outfit?
It looks...
like it doesn't quite fit.
This outfit is so important.
Why isn't it finished yet?
Qingyu had an emergency that day.
Qingyi tried on the suit for him.
They have different builds.
How could the tailor
get the measurements right?
All he does is make trouble.
Qingyi was just trying to help me.
It's not his fault.
Miss Fang,
have you chosen your wedding dress?
The wedding dress I originally chose
was replaced by Qingyi.
Was there something wrong
with the original wedding dress?
The original dress was too plain.
It didn't suit Miss Fang's
bootlicker vibe.
Qingyi.
Qingyi is just envious of us.
After we get married,
I'll help Mother
arrange the wedding
for Qingyi and Miss Huo.
Who said I'm going to marry Huo Minxian?
Marriage is a serious matter, not a joke.
It's fine.
If Qingyi really doesn't like Miss Huo,
as his sister-in-law,
I'll help him look for a suitable match
among the noble ladies in Nancheng.
He'll definitely find someone he likes.
Yeah.
Sister-in-law and Qingyu
are getting married soon.
It's a pity that Qingyu
still hasn't seen
her true colors.
What nonsense are you talking about?
How is it nonsense?
She's not Fang...
Why is this dress torn?
It was perfectly fine when we packed it.
Who else could it be?
Let me see.
Why is it torn like this?
It's fine.
Mother,
we can have another wedding dress made.
You suspect me too?
Apologize to your sister-in-law.
What if I don't?
Are you going to kill me today?
Did you do nothing wrong?
Whether I was wrong or not,
didn't you already send me to prison
3 years ago?
Qingyi,
these are two different matters.
I personally witnessed several times
that you targeted your sister-in-law.
It doesn't matter
if you have a problem with me.
If you want to vent your anger,
don't take it out on innocent people.
Innocent people?
She's innocent?
Fine.
Everyone is innocent.
I'm the only one who was born a bad seed!
I'm the shame of the Murong family!
Are you happy now?
No one said that.
But that's what you did.
You didn't believe me 3 years ago,
and you still don't believe me now.
Do you deserve to be my older brother?
Shut up!
Is that how you talk to your brother?
Since you were a child,
Qingyu has always been
cleaning up your messes.
If it weren't for him,
would you even have a place
in the Murong family?
Is the Murong family anything good?
Do you really think I want to be a Mu—
Get out!
Bastard!
Hurry up and take it back.
Miss Fang,
hurry up and choose another one.
On behalf of Qingyi,
I apologize to you.
He is a bit hot-tempered,
but he means no harm.
Maybe he feels that lately
you've taken away my attention,
so he's throwing a childish tantrum.
Perhaps.
People of the Murong family, get out here!
Your Murong family
is truly shameless.
Marshal Li.
Back then, Peilin supported you,
who came from a humble background.
You were so attentive at that time.
Now that Peilin
is dead
and the real killer is still at large,
you dare to throw your weight around
in the Murong family?
Do you really think there's no one left
Even if there is, they are useless.
Uncle Li,
please make yourself clear.
What exactly is this?
Murong Qingyi was abused by those bastards
from the Huo family for 3 years
and had the tendons in his hands severed.
So you experienced
more than what you told me.
This was...
This was in prison, wasn't it?
What else could it have been?
Cheng Jinzhi,
your own son spent 3 years in prison
being abused by the Huo family,
and they even severed
the tendons in his hands.
Now,
you're letting him
be the Huo family's son-in-law?
Your Murong family
is truly adaptable.
I was sold for a good price by you.
Who's the one being embarrassed here?
If you are unhappy,
you might send me to prison again
for another several years.
I can't afford that.
Family?
Is this a family?
Your Murong family
might be able to swallow this,
[According to the Huo family's order,
we followed Mao to the prison.]
but I can't.
[While Murong Qingyi was defenseless,
I held down his head]
[and shoulders, and Mao severed...]
I was fighting on the front lines.
How dare the Huo family
secretly plot against my man?
Regarding this matter,
he killed someone first.
It was understandable
for the Huo family to vent their anger.
Understandable?
Your Murong family is prestigious,
yet you let the Huo family
mess with him in prison.
When I sent this kid back,
he was in one piece.
Twelve years.
In just 12 years,
he was labeled a killer,
served prison time,
and had his tendons severed.
Who else should I blame but your family?
Qingyu!
Where are you going?
What exactly do you want?
I'm telling you,
you must give me an explanation today.
A member of our Murong family
was hurt by the Huo family.
Why should we give the Li family
an explanation?
You should know whose toes
you're stepping on.
If word gets out,
people will think the Huo family
dares to walk all over me.
I would lose face.
Let me tell you this, Cheng.
Give me 200 boxes of rifle bullets,
and I'll let this go.
So, Marshal Li,
after all that talk about justice,
you are actually here to blackmail us?
Servants.
See the guest out!
I don't mind if this ends up
in the newspapers tomorrow
and everyone in Nancheng finds out
that the Murong family
got their youngest son crippled
and forced him to marry their enemy,
all just to get some planes
for their eldest son.
If this problem can be solved
with 200 boxes of rifle bullets,
you should...
think twice.
[Renxin Orphanage]
Let's go! Stop unloading the goods!
Let's go drink!
-Let’s go.
This is a girl's hair?
Boss Hai.
Inspector Li,
you and I are really destined.
How come
we meet in a slum
like this?
So Boss Hai, you know this is a slum?
Then why are you here?
You are so bossy, Inspector Li.
If you can come, why can't I?
I'm here to investigate a case.
What case?
Boss Hai,
are you interrogating the police?
Then what do you want to ask me?
Nanny Sun from Renxin Orphanage
is missing.
Do you know
about this?
I don't know her.
And I don't know about this.
Really?
I heard that whenever
Nanny Sun from Renxin Orphanage
returns to Nancheng,
she goes to Dongjiadu to do charity work.
And coincidentally,
you were seen at both
the aviation school's opening ceremony
she attended
and Dongjiadu.
Boss Hai,
isn't this a bit too coincidental?
Do you solve cases based on coincidence?
No wonder the case clearance rate
goes up so quickly.
I often come here to volunteer
and help some poor children.
So you have such a kind heart.
I was born into poverty.
I owe everything I have today
to the support of my fans.
Naturally,
I can't forget where I came from.
But Inspector Li,
is everyone
in the police station like you,
privileged young masters
who grew up in comfort and luxury,
never having suffered
a hard day in their lives?
No wonder in this world,
good people receive no reward,
and bad people face no consequences.
Watch your words, Boss Hai.
I think
since I became a police officer,
I haven't slacked off for a single day.
Fools aren't scary.
What's scary are hardworking fools.
But still, I like fools.
Inspector Li, I advise you
to go back to being
the wealthy young master you are.
An upright official who speaks for the people
doesn't suit you.
When it comes to
the suffering of the people,
I'm afraid
Young Master Qingyi
understands better than you.
Have you found him?
Where is Qingyu?
Young Master Qingyu
searched the passenger transport,
docks, and stations,
but couldn't find him.
We also checked
Young Master Qingyi's residence.
He hasn't been back.
The rain is getting heavier.
Tell Qingyu to come back
and wait for news.
The rest of you can keep looking.
Young Master refused
and asked me to report back.
He went to Young Master Qingyi's garden
on Hongmei Road.
Marshal Li,
why don't you go back first?
I've already had someone
send the telegram
to inventory the supplies.
Qingyi is not a three-year-old child.
He's just temporarily out of touch.
What's there to worry about?
His mother isn't even worried,
so why should others be?
What kind of talk is that?
Human talk.
I'm going to pray.
Serve tea for Marshal Li.
Marshal Li can leave
whenever he wants.
Young Master Qingyi
is quite like you, Marshal Li.
How so?
Unscrupulous
and sharp-tongued.
Now I know
who he learned it from.
What are you trying to say?
You've already got what you wanted.
What are you still waiting for?
I could tell when we last met
that you are actually
the one who knows Qingyi best.
You came today
not only for
those 200 boxes of rifle bullets,
but also to stand up for Qingyi,
right?
You think you're very smart, don't you?
People say you are
rough and unreasonable,
but they don't know
you are very meticulous.
My little cleverness
is nothing in front of you.
But whether it is for Qingyi's grievance
or your dignity,
the Huo family
must pay the price.
Otherwise,
wouldn't anyone dare
to challenge you?
What do you want?
The Elite Club—
what kind of organization is it?
Where is it?
And how do I get in?
What?
You want to take down the Huo family?
You think you alone can do that?
For the Murong family
to attack the Huo family
for Qingyi right now
would be unrealistic.
Moreover, in this family,
the people who really care
if Qingyi lives or dies
are very few.
For you to take action
would be unjustified,
and the cost would be too high.
An outsider like me
has no such concerns.
Rest assured.
Whether I succeed or fail,
it has nothing to do with you.
What are you after?
I'm after justice.
Do you believe it?
Justice?
You overestimated yourself.
I heard
when you came to the Murong family,
♪ Sharper pain, deeper mark ♪
it was quite a big scene.
♪ Deeper care, greater torment ♪
Rather than letting
your dowry and betrothal gifts
♪ I won't give up on you ♪
♪ Don't let go of me ♪
sit idle,
♪ Let the ropes of fate ♪
you might as well put them
in the Huo family's treasury.
♪ Bind you and me ♪
Treasury?
♪ Even if led to a precipice ♪
♪ Together, we fall ♪